<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gamification</string>
    <string name="textoA">Hi, my name is Rob Willian</string>
    <string name="ContentDescriptionTexto">Text</string>
    <string name="aex01">is a data structure that contains a group of elements. Typically these elements are all of the same data type, such as an integer or string.</string>
    <string name="bex01">is a subset of algebra used for creating true/false statements.</string>
    <string name="dex01">" is a signal sent to a host that requests a response. It serves two primary purposes: 1) to check if the host is available and 2) to measure how long the response takes."</string>
    <string name="eex01">"is a whole number (not a fraction) that can be positive, negative, or zero. "</string>
    <string name="cex01">is a data type used in programming, such as an integer and floating point unit, but is used to represent text rather than numbers.</string>
    <string name="TitloCompleteAsFrases">Complete the sentences</string>
    <string name="ex01">Answer the questions with the answers below.</string>
    <string name="opex02">"String; Integer; Ping; Array ; Boolean   "</string>
    <string name="confirmar">Confirm</string>
    <string name="Total">Total</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pontuacao">Punctuation</string>
    <string name="titulo_inicio">Computer Technical Terms</string>
    <string name="bt_home_lets_go">Let\'s go</string>
    <string name="content_descricao">initial burglary image</string>
    <string name="img_mapinha">Map image</string>
    <string name="imagem_robo_mapa">image of theft on the map</string>
    <string name="botao_proximo">Next</string>
    <string name="titulo_mapa_progresso">Progress</string>
    <string name="bt_facil">Easy</string>
    <string name="bt_medio">Medium</string>
    <string name="bt_dificil">Hard</string>
    <string name="img_qtd_vidas">image of lives</string>
    <string name="msg_result">Result!</string>
    <string name="bt_voltar">Come back</string>
    <string name="insira_nome">Enter your name</string>
    <string name="atv9ex1">Program that functions as an interface between the hardware and the operating system, indicating the equipment available and available for certain functions.</string>
    <string name="atv9ex2">An industrial specification for wireless personal networking areas. Provides a way to connect and exchange information between devices such as mobile phones.</string>
    <string name="atv9ex3">Part of a user\'s information, stored in the browser, that is available to the server to identify it.</string>
    <string name="atv9ex4">Mechanism that allows bridging between two networks that work as different protocols.</string>
    <string name="atv9ex5">Script language for Web publishing, which allows simple programming instructions to be inserted.</string>
    <string name="msgSair">Are you sure you want to quit ?</string>
    <string name="msgAlerta">"Alert! "</string>
    <string name="msgNao">"No "</string>
    <string name="msgSim">"Yes "</string>
    <string name="msgReiniciar">"Reset Module "</string>
    <string name="msgHits">"Hits: "</string>
    <string name="msgNext">"Next "</string>
    <string name="msgGameOver">"Game Over "</string>
    <string name="msgTryAgain">"Try Again "</string>
    <string name="msgRetry">"Retry "</string>
    <string name="msgGamerOL">"Game Over! Lifes: "</string>
    <string name="msgYouDie">"You Died "</string>
    <string name="msgParabens">"Congratulations "</string>
    <string name="txtJogodaMemoria">Memory game</string>
    <string name="txt_termosTecnicos">Technical terms</string>
    <string name="textoB">Let\'s play now?</string>
    <string name="faq_1">There are 10 phases and each phase has 5 questions, each question is worth one point, which in total corresponds to 50 points</string>
    <string name="tt_faq">Evaluation method</string>
    <string name="faq_2">If you miss a question you lose a life.</string>
    <string name="faq_3">If you return a stage your points will be divided by 2 at the end of the game, for each time you return.</string>
    <string name="faq_4">If you lose your life the game is over.</string>
    <string name="faq_5">In case you restart the phase the lives that you lost in the same phase will be recovered if they have not finished but that will imply in your points, at the end of the game the total will be divided by 2 each time you use the return function.</string>
</resources>